# RALPH KEMP

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

## EXPERIENCE

#### Le Wagon

Teaching assistant

After finishing Le Wagon, I was asked to return to be a teaching assistant to help new students. I am teaching classes which focus on both front and back end web development.

Oct 2017 - present

#### Meteor.me

Full Stack Developer

In a team of 4, I helped create Meteor, a mobile-first web app focusing on hyper-local university dating for our final project at Le Wagon. I was responsible for both front and back end development using Rails. We presented it in September at Google Campus in London.

Sep 2017

#### Deliveroo

Customer Services Representative

This included helping customers on the phone with orders, assisting drivers, and advising restaurants on specific issues. I was also regularly put in charge of the online orders and online support team in the office, which included overseeing the management of calls relating to specific orders/issues. September 2015 - January 2016

#### **H Bauer Publishing**

Graphic Designer

Freelance design work in the Design Hub at H Bauer Publishing, Working on layouts for magazines including Bella, Take a Break: Fate & Fortune, and Wonderpedia.

July 2015

#### Eye magazine

I was a regular editorial assistant on this graphic design title, edited by John L Walters. Duties included editing and uploading content on the website, selecting and adding events to the magazine's listings, checking and captioning pictures, photographing book content for online reviews, and assisting at live events such as 'Type Tuesday' at St Bride's. Office duties also included data inputing, uploading web content, and speaking with sales partners on the phone.

2013 - 15

#### Avila Secondary School, Spain

English language assistant

2011

## **EDUCATION**

#### Le Wagon - Coding Bootcamp

Jul-Sep 2017

I took part in an intensive 9 week long coding bootcamp to truly throw myself into the world of web development. The course focused on studying Ruby on Rails, Javascript, jQuery, SQL, PostgreSQL, MVC architecture, Git, Github, OOP, Heroku, HTML and CSS. All of these new skills were then used in 2 projects, Safari-Now, and Meteor, a university dating app which I created with 3 other teammates.

## University of Kent, Canterbury BA joint honours

2011-2015

Spanish and History of Art. (2:1)

#### Haberdashers' Aske's Hatcham College

2004-2011

2011: 3 A levels: Art (B), Spanish (A), Music Technology (C) 2009: 9 GCSEs: Art (A), Graphics (B), English Language (A), English Literature (A), Spanish (A), Music (A), Maths (B), Double Science (BB)

# ABOUT ME

Front end web developer, music producer, and lover of all things creative. My skills include Ruby on Rails, Javascript/jQuery, HTML5 and CSS, and I am currently learning React/Redux. I've been writing and producing music for the past 10 years, mainly using Logic Pro X. I also speak Spanish, and am studying Korean.

### contact

9 Ashmead Road, London, SE8 4DY

M: 07447088747

E:RalphK3mp@gmail.com

W: RalphKemp.com

#### Social:

Linkedin.com/in/ralphkemp Instagram.com/ralphk3mp